let questions = [
    {
        question: "Тут какой-то вопрос 1?",
        answer1: "1: Ответ 1",
        answer2: "2: Ответ 2",
        answer3: "3: Ответ 3",
        answer4: "4: Ответ 4",
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Тут какой-то вопрос 2?",
        answer1: "1: Ответ 1",
        answer2: "2: Ответ 2",
        answer3: "3: Ответ 3",
        answer4: "4: Ответ 4",
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Тут какой-то вопрос 3?",
        answer1: "1: Ответ 1",
        answer2: "2: Ответ 2",
        answer3: "3: Ответ 3",
        answer4: "4: Ответ 4",
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Тут какой-то вопрос 4?",
        answer1: "1: Ответ 1",
        answer2: "2: Ответ 2",
        answer3: "3: Ответ 3",
        answer4: "4: Ответ 4",
        correct: 4
    },
    {
        question: "Тут какой-то вопрос 5?",
        answer1: "1: Ответ 1",
        answer2: "2: Ответ 2",
        answer3: "3: Ответ 3",
        answer4: "4: Ответ 4",
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Тут какой-то вопрос 6?",
        answer1: "1: Ответ 1",
        answer2: "2: Ответ 2",
        answer3: "3: Ответ 3",
        answer4: "4: Ответ 4",
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Тут какой-то вопрос 7?",
        answer1: "1: Ответ 1",
        answer2: "2: Ответ 2",
        answer3: "3: Ответ 3",
        answer4: "4: Ответ 4",
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Тут какой-то вопрос 8?",
        answer1: "1: Ответ 1",
        answer2: "2: Ответ 2",
        answer3: "3: Ответ 3",
        answer4: "4: Ответ 4",
        correct: 4
    },
    {
        question: "Тут какой-то вопрос 9?",
        answer1: "1: Ответ 1",
        answer2: "2: Ответ 2",
        answer3: "3: Ответ 3",
        answer4: "4: Ответ 4",
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Тут какой-то вопрос 10?",
        answer1: "1: Ответ 1",
        answer2: "2: Ответ 2",
        answer3: "3: Ответ 3",
        answer4: "4: Ответ 4",
        correct: 2
    },
];

